MARY. MARY.
The narrow. Narrow.
Narrow. In the
America. Now.
The all.
The follow or are
the AM
married
. The girl.
You're.
Older
or
or little.
Old.
An arrow.
A given to you without the hope that
a boy the simple fact is I'm shit in the
CROSSFIRE with the cops and once I meet my
needs even at the other the ball I'm going
for me. So I'm the guy who knows that
you're the one who took the
twenty bands and my did
a cover of the directed killer got
a cigarette Danny Boy and my proposition
is quick and easy we spit the twenty five
for you fifteen for me and I take
it I'm gonna live and it's my.
God that you open your right
daddy's paper to be pried.
The bricks and then he put
the eyes. Of.
The in.
The IT.
Where the police it's been
a murder. They've
been inspected. Like all the times
in the middle of the night yeah.
That's your garden alright yeah well I've
been doing much faster by now and then at
this minute for him yeah there's another
day where the doc says you sir it's OK.
To knock over yes I did inspect this guy's
name Frank Johnson it was around here
claim he was out working his drug.
Mr Johnson spect it's almost
a detail then you had a
front seat I sure did get
a look at the killer too good at street
light was right on his face when he got out
of its current shot it shot at twice.
Missed think it recognizing the sign again
it's not
a face I'm likely to forget he came out
of the lineup I think. What's this all
about and that man Joe Barton is going to
testify before the grand jury next week
that's not too bad reckon you know too
much about Smiley Freeman you know who's
monitoring that is the guy that's right
Gordon is our witness now your it me.
Or you have to do is identify
the killer with the rest of my.
Body of being in
a way you are aren't you. Right
over that one thirty six Out
to Linda apartment or the Johnson OK I
don't wake her up she's not going to like
it should want to know what you are watching
taking it out ahead what it is what.
You see what you mean where you're
standing when he shot it right.
Well I was right down there with the dog
when the car drove up I didn't pay much
attention to a little bit later heard
a shot I looked up just in time to see
this fellow what's his name out of the car
then the killer bumped another shot right
into my block he got out of the car
started shooting me I need although I kind
of guy I don't know like they all look
alike to me while the same was alright
it was just sure that they're on target.
It's not your shadow when you. When
you go call read. Maybe you
won't miss next that will be
a next time but suppose you don't get
a conviction and would like to spend the
rest of my life with police protection or
wind up on a sidewalk like him What
are you worried about him is. There
a minute to get the rest of the story
down town. I hate to get mixed up in
this it's getting so
a man has to be careful where there's no
good these days. When. I think I don't
mind my somewhere around here is that OK
if I look or remember where you're headed
now you know it was right over here no
amount of money if you get outta here when.
You. Think it's mighty bring
everybody connected but I'm in
a lineup see if John King and identify
anybody I want everybody to do says no lies
I want everybody to see if we can pick up
anything on that somebody may have seen
it.
JOHNSON That's not your husband man was
killed they saw happen right over here
sorry I had to get Jad a bad job after
all they had to make sure that they had
a wide. Just
a product I can pick up. Just like
you are always running away you mean
always running away running away from
everything broadcast descriptions like male
American which French
called soft brown had
a very ordinary looking. Yam But how would
you describe your husband Mrs Johnson.
I haven't been able to
a long time man I go now
the monument. I station.
I want everything shut off from black to
everything I stick but they're right.
You hear the shots fired that I was that
sounds. Fine to pictures I don't want to
hurt just charge naturally. They
won't do anybody any good but keep.
Books on psychology I wonder why they got
a problem I wouldn't
know if he's going to.
Buy smoke or. What does that mean nothing
oh he's got two suits one of which is wearing
what he got what he looks like nobody
pays any attention to him anyway not even
is why you're really wasting your time
there must be at least twenty thousand
men in San Francisco the last of that
description how are you going to find
it has to be something different about
a different anyway from other people
there is something different about it
something different about everybody and
we're going to do so we find out what it is
now you see our problem is down to what
I want to help but I'm not the what you
want to do I want to go answer
a few questions go ahead ask where does
he generally go when he's not at home I
haven't since idea as you know relatives
in this area I know were his friends I
don't know if the dog found
a mutual friend you always go to sleep when
he walked the dog sometimes he goes to
sleep I love that the. Inspectors are
a couple more. Well I'm
terribly sorry there's been
a mistake medic wants to take an OK Remember
to an age of thirty five and forty two
is out and that is when the trenchcoat snap
Ramphele all I'm five foot eleven when
I didn't seventy and all I'm scared to
answer questions the domestic situation in
this time of terrible. Gets.
Well let's get going.
Don't you read anything but dog food he's
not particular and I'm lazy so we eat out
where when I see the quantity and still
they love to go with the water the way in
that neighborhood and when
to get real Thank you ma'am
a little rascal. Usually we're creatures
of habit I'm afraid check your email or
not enough will be able but that's OK because
I get along well I don't explain this
at home what's going on and
I'm sorry there's been
a mistake you saw it when I
got all my life. But I do
know I haven't thought about it and I
sit down and we don't have to have
a reason then you want to have
a decent picture of your husband no he
doesn't have to take I don't want any
photographs of him floating around that
might get in the papers the killer doesn't
know what he looks like didn't
know he shot a shadow shot shot
a prank right nobody knows that
except the killer the now use
a let's keep it that way it's important
he's really endangered that worry I thought
you were beyond worrying about him I didn't
say that if he doesn't give himself up
you're really going to have something to
worry about we've got to protect it like
you did the other witness killed are to
be alive right now at the end that is why
your friend and I are. Description for Frank
Johnson as the nail found nice to take
medicine for these four I don't know we
just might take vitamin coach Not that I
think. What's up there
to tell my husband and
I I thought you said you worked
hard on. This place now and.
Then Brant get down you know you're not
allowed that they have. Run brand is the
nearest we could ever get to owning one
bank's literature we found that sitting on
the street corner one night waiting for
someone to dusting they recognize each
other right away.
This supposed to be you. It was
a lovely awesome day the wind was blowing
through my hair. It was all very charming
but that was four years ago that was
Frank Cyprus for important period we're.
Going to have a get
together firstly that I'm
a friend of the man he wanted I was off
work for I have five thousand two thousand
and talent they're asked to come out he
became restless so we went to Tulsa New
Mexico where he painted Indians. And then.
Then he got out of England so he went
back to listen to waiting in order to try
and find Did he ever do is help or you
know I can tell that much of. What
you do these in Pennsylvania.
Now I get restless again so we can't sentences
here instead is different from meals
there it is and around wars
missions in general that was
a social protest that money around had
to take down couldn't sell the stuff he
wouldn't trust him to do was that enough
the sketchbook to fill but I just never
got around. To try to get
a job why should I. Mind. Bending.
Now that is burlesque now that I like it's
pretty good yes but it takes was not to
have
a career you have to have staying power
prices with this so when the money ran out
we just clicked. On some density
move in Chinatown room.
He's a retired variable temp to get
a sense of just the beach. I know that
is that Rembrandt. What is all this
got to do fine thank you just answer the
question that is another why should it
have. Been done that if you want to snoop
into their lane to buy Mary to put the
you. Don't. Set your eyes upon our Yes
but keep on talking.
Oh no oh hello friend. No. I'm
fine to interrupt but if I were
you I'd have the police to
thank you no call. I know I
have. Heard Music was not music
you didn't do you are going to
pay for Mr JOHNSON It's
bad enough to be alone in
a big city with no place to go but as soon
as the newspapers at the street and I
cannot find out he didn't
get drives didn't have
a guidebook environ with guns if I had
eyes when I wanted to get rid of I'd do
exactly what you did if he wants to run
away that's his business and your business
to Mrs Johnson I'll be seeing.
No wonder the world full of bachelors
a. Little more needling
is all she needs to be
a robot keeper failed she wants to get rid
of wandering curious even Matt Damon go
after him Monday a good
a lot of the town like
a. Friend of mine that is
particularly on well I know story.
She told. What. Is already
going to press the look of the
murder now what is life
like in the filth they are
a tad like sex stuff like I give
a dollar in the morning I
hope for the favorites. Or
are.
Or want one
or
are
the
poor.
Or are.
You coming out of going to the police smile
when you say that I report. Newspaper.
That to what nigger well. Are
you just going to leave me
dangling here just so I literally never
get out of the pleasure Mr if you are Mr
Johnson if you know I'm
amazed what you might not.
But magic I possess
a moment ago total strangers now you know
my out so it's love at first sight now
show me how you got there without
police to get story after I got out.
Looks like half the
police force is down the.
Mustang just look straight ahead like you
did when you got mad. Incidentally my
name is like like in the graphic we've got
a dandy little sheet all full of
Google would go around every. Day by.
And.
There was something. Disturbing him out
of one thing judge my love the joy you
think you're going to give you
the police to let you know Mr M.
An old. Boy about the play don't you get
a lot. About
the story we'll get the story from my
husband is safe and sound the tape but he
will be safe and sound if we got the feel
of an image Oh God do you wish something
to let me have
a bourbon or. Why did you come in tonight
Mrs Johnson or should not because I like
if you didn't by any chance come to me
Tell your husband that you boys got
a far fetched supposition position but I
stopped using it for syllable words it
won't be working for the graphic
anymore what your husband is
a dunce I don't know if you together I
don't know if we did but it is up to the
ticket counter being to go to any choice
about how much you. Want to Be nice to me
as it does and who knows I might
even be able to help you I'm not
a bad guy when you get to know me not just
perhaps but place now to answer yes or
no has been sold into the land right right
and you are right you may be in here I
had the slightest idea I came down to
crunch twenty songs and I heard music that
only about in this joint
something to eat no thanks I'm
a boy try shoving no really into. How are.
You going to do you find your husband with
my help give me an exclusive for twenty
four hours I get my baby
a paper tiger benefits and first time buy
and if I can and then try to win the
rebate for the usual procedure coppers
follow on second thought This is Jeff and
you very attractive I may try and when you
read up you know something about the B.
But very mercenary of the good I like
my snappy one. The title I know.
They all are. Funny sure.
Graham maybe but that will be by the time
I get through building up Frank and if
you want to get ready to bring it with
me just tell me where and when I want
president thing until I've gotta.
Think that we're going to. In the
spirit conclusion of all that for you or
your husband so much. Trouble if you don't
look at that I can't.
Find anything like the back on those they
were mad at me because the show through
the night bringing in
a new actor telling the people it's terrific
that's about the age of twenty anybody
can spell the people of course run
to bring in the show here but
a little plug help. If you like to thank
next time you come to the night show but
really don't and then I'll be right
and. FRANK So tonight you know
I'm. Going to turn your husband when you
see the given cell phone may be out of the
.
Right down. When I go into the room now
I'm going to practice and give them
something to think about though in that
case I'll disappear let's not get too much
think about well if I need you I'll get
all you want to get in touch with Johnson
just look around I'll be
there that night to let the.
What are you doing nice going down the
next time you try to get out more trouble.
I've got news for you. I've just seen your
husband's doctor why aren't you feeling
well your husband is a hypochondriac
he's a very sick man he's got
a bad heart. I don't believe I've dug
a hole. Frank.
Maybe figured you wouldn't be as. Well
you can walk into any drug store and buy
some medicine not without a prescription
a candid I've never noticed every drug store
in town that none of this medicine be
dispensed without in order for me. To have
an attack and not have that within you
know what that means you can't do that if
it's the only way I can get him to come
in and testify I mean the pranks done
nothing wrong it was in the wrong place at
the wrong time I thought the police were
supposed to protect people not put them in
danger all it says in my book history is
that the good of the majority has got to
be upheld and for the good of the majority
Frank Janssen's that the five really
gives himself up by supply of medicine
we're protected and it doesn't have
a heart attack or a bullet from on a
smiley Braman man I don't believe
a word you're saying you're only trying to
frighten and I'm getting pretty sick of
you know get out of here of course if you
want to try to find it I won't try to
stop it I don't think you can find. I don't
think he's running away from us I think
he's running away from you I said get out.
I wired in my selections from the what
do you buy giving this additional supply
that would be giving you no feeling of guilt
thank you that the excitement of last
night your husband and daughter to use the
empty was getting to be so you see my
action is not prompted by kindness So Mike
is reluctant to gamble with that man's
life. It is hard really that that the
Franks condition isn't any worse than
thousands of man it's turning their hearts
running in technique misguided believe
that they were building up their bodies
that only his heart could control what do
you think for the past year your husband
has and hypertension that complicates
matters hypertension what causes that I'm
not sure my get over and happiness in
science the but you know more about it
than I do why should I But naturally you
must know about his double families doctors
you know he's right so yes I'm not her
selfish vicious wife because it isn't happen
if the cause of this they are is that
what he told you is that what he tells
everyone Frank didn't discuss his faggot
life to mean one of the like you have to
get it from you I can explain to you his
condition and that's or has a
cardiac condition that's called it
a next alone is not COD He also has
hypertension it's going to why X. Plus Y.
Is dangerous and why another Psychiatry
says Johnson ideal only perfect explants
why equal a steady deterioration X.
Minus that is an improvement and what you
and your husband do about it to consider
my only personal concern right now is to
get the sandhills doing if you see him
tell him you should give yourself up
imperative to think that. Given the fact you
know it sounds intelligent.
Prank calling I thought I'd never talk and
not say right now be back inside this
explained everything. All right
trying to come off climb
a bit JOHNSON Yeah and I suppose that isn't
Joe wife either that was his Were do
you have any identification yes I have
my name is Stephen Carruthers our father
while we're on the subject I think
you better have your I think that.
Still Frank is a fugitive from the law
well that's just like he's still had
a venturous adventure FRANK Oh yes and
the one Mrs Johnson I guess you never
visited our workshop before
what makes you think he's
a printer but he is all of places he's
gone and all the things he's done you know
my life has been pretty uneventful straight
from high school of this job from my
rooming house to the streetcar line down
here we're in the evening back to my
roommate house again but since he's been
here it's different he may. My kind of
exciting I never get tired of listening the
stories he tells about his trip down to
Mexico when he was wandering around with
all those bullfighters and when he shipped
off to time he and that all freighter and
then jumped ship on Star and I suppose
you heard the stories many times Mrs Johnson
I never heard them never to he didn't
well maybe he didn't want his wife to know.
Sorry if I told her turn of course you
have chosen to mail being here why
yes yes then why Frank that me
a letter and tell you Oh he did I don't
know what Mr Anderson's going to say when
he finds out Frank isn't coming
in today you know he's got
a terrible disposition he doesn't exercise
enough course I don't either but then
well I'm going to protect Frank he saved
my job once you know Mr Anderson was going
to fire me but Frank said if Mr made us
go you can pay me off to where they had
a terrible argument they even took it up
stairs to Mr Winston were still here Frank
was to. Look and they don't tell
anyone about that letter the county
Oh no no no you can trust me not even the
police the police coming they're very
apt to but just don't mention the letter
or anything about my being at all. Good I
am at the scene and people that do it
with refrain don't try they may but you
better get the lead on going up stairs as
an one is top OK I'll be right up is the
mailing at all July no one's People sometimes
I think it would be better for Frank
if he got himself fired when he doesn't
belong around here look at all the time he
puts in these mannequins. Is
something like you live in
that the way well it may be
a little severe but it shows he was thinking
about you anyway yet the money they
don't want to get to Dana. We've been
frank here no no he's late Was there
a letter for No I just said new song I
want to hear from twenty one of the two
missing brother if I got
a question that man. No matter all that
there's got to be one well maybe it'll be
here on the afternoon my or three o'clock
if one comes home. And let's just say
that I shall.
One of the guys at work is going to get
a regional power like I have and think
this idea I wouldn't get to sit with that
guy if I were you it
crucifies grandmother for
a story I haven't found them is objectionable
if you are what right if you prying
it's my personal life having
the fall of is if I were
a criminal I'm sick of it I'm sick of you
and I want to stop this if John didn't
your husband ever beat you are you going
to have these men about following makes
a man to tell Joe Gordon isn't stupid
if I'm smart enough to use you with
a brick doesn't need to see our house and
so is he you may be very happy to have
a cop around before this thing is
over that I've done. That with
a bucket of those are
already had like that.
From me this morning all I'm trying to do
was help you to know the truth doesn't
shadow. Wow. Right.
By the way if you let it. Run don't
download it on the page board for good
journalism don't you worry about
a put down like this don't have to know you
should live it was very careless and I
have
a quiz these guys do you always open other
people's mail. And Jessica said it took
a lot of the female impersonator they've
got following you know. Well it's the
current get down to business and back
turn less than an expat then right up the
alley OK.
OK. OK.
Meaning to ask something because I'm not
sure what you mean about the doctor.
Medicine needs but I have
a bad idea that we've got to have these
pills and can't get them anywhere the
police seem to that. The first is smart. I
don't know I stuck to it and
sit down and pick the bench.
Right the police will probably read this
note so I can't tell you or be but if you
think back you know where to find me than
my mind reader if you flew this next one
. Of the out there but under the sun in
a place like the one where I first lost
to. Things like the scared of security
always talking like this
with murder. You know Mrs J.
You have this pretty clever guy that you
don't think so but he is he's testing it
is asking you to admit
that your marriage is
a failure that you are for saying that he
understands you but that you don't live
with the leg of the rhetoric I've had just
about enough they are wise men in the
past ten hours I've met three men three
men who all put together I haven't known
Frank for one fraction of the length of
time I have yet they all know him better
than I do along the way I found out
a few things like I found out how Frank
Johnson really feels about that at the
first chance based excuse he took on ran
he didn't even think enough of me to
confide in me that it was then at the store
in the face of those manic I thought he
really sees that me all right it's OK if
that's the way you know about it but he
wanted them to have to come out of hiding
and get them. What did you have to break
significant cigarette butts to get every
last season vile that is OK This place is
the best welcome top but I mean
every the squid is always better on
a full tummy. About
another thing. That I've
got to soften up assistance something that
I have that doesn't have to punch the
one up for the money I promise you are
much doing it for yourself the challenge.
You've got to accept that it's right I
really would like to find if only I could
decipher the riddle in this letter to get
that we can do it that letters like like
drawing
a graph one landed from last night the other
leads back into the bank but you have
to wear the cross has been it. You need
a manicure. So I do you know this the first
time my life I ever insisted on helping
a woman find
a house that I live by the way what do
people call you the side leg of the gravel.
People like me going
with any boy. Danny Boy
and. Fisherman's Wharf
Frank used to come here
a lot I remember once he did
a water color of a bird
a fisherman and my friend just gave it
to. Not to be outdone the fisherman gave
Frank a big swordfish I made a
remark about the joys of living with
a part of the system and we had
a better world where he certainly wasn't
the first do you think Frank was referring
to
a girl when he said monster what else.
Another one got it up here on Telegraph Hill
find it
a can here but I thought it was wonderful
and I told him so insinuated that my
taste not rent
a calendar I said my taste was my own and
I wanted the paper so he gave it to me
but he signed it Illinois husband. Without
telling him I admittedly contest they
were having here the odds are with the oil
violinist has been one for Sprite five
hundred dollars but do you think Frank
was pleased when he found the home no he
refused the money and withdrew the
painting that he was already sounds pretty
stubborn stupidly stubborn I wonder if he
ever really wanted to be successful. Soon
after that he took the job at heart and
went you know the only thing we know for
sure is that Frank was at the Oriental gods
last hour in the neighborhood Let's go
out then yeah he sat around the sick room
until we came down to do the one o'clock
show and he said he was like
make a phone call then factor up
a ladder he said to get in touch with you
that he was going to send a letter to
a store care for Mr may have
a liking for should be surprised I've been
there but didn't say what he was going
to do or where he might feel I didn't
want to say why don't you try some of the
soul of the grand runs
a bar across the street coming up short you
can go down the back stairs I know I've
seen you before. I was sure I was in earnest
does not mean the picture the Frank.
To. Me Something like you know
how banks are drawing pictures.
With this my. And was known to own
a president of the common lot of oh well
let me back and then I wouldn't said so
use the quick yack you. Do still have the
picture maybe I could read in the paper
that the Democrats are going to keep saying
you sure you want to help on run. Why
not again that plug in the paper about us
we can show you what can you take from
the top. I got to see our agent.
Heard about this place for
years I've been to four.
What you have folks done
very special they did
a congressman cabbage orig for you know
for general rock for the lady you know
fashion for me they are called favorites
if any is broken you get more out of him
alone anyway oh I wish you were I
had I looked funny when I arrived
Oh good now I think up in the glow.
Yes Mrs Johnson from what you said last
night just before closing time did he say
Wayne was going No we didn't just buy ten
bucks maybe I should tell you it was
a couple of dollars in here this morning
asking about Frank followed that you
couldn't very well say mind your own
business to some sort of trouble message and
some you didn't come home last night rod
like I've been looking for mine three
years. Glad I finally met your mom
I often wondered what kind of
a woman Frank was married to not that I
met him he was too easy to being so quiet
and strange times for instance now look at
this picture. He put on front pages for
me about six weeks ago if you don't think
Patrick's Day But look at the date on the
nineteen forty seven Well I should post
it not just print which March seventeenth
ranks but nineteen twenty. We spent the
day on the beach if I have this point
then we suddenly decide I had to see this
and that from the top of my return to San
Francisco we had
a car then we had champagne cocktails and
much of the sense of the Golden Gate
after all it was Frank's
payday and St Patrick's we had
a beautiful day and I don't drink coffee
on the Amiga when we told that to come
around to some kind of. There's nothing
like being young and in love and get asked
to build that to boot to get people to
try to do crazy things on their birthday
this year we didn't I went to
a movie thanking down he painted that
picture. Now I know what Frank meant when he
said someone should have been
in the picture with him.
I have
a notion if your husband could have seen
your face when you were talking about that
nine hundred forty seven it appeared to
right smack in the middle of that picture
with his arms around. Cyrus or Mr Leggett
the graphic with the Sullivan is helping
me look for Frank I freshen up
a little what if all the garbage you know
I'm trying. To get something something I
hadn't counted on but. Thanks to let's
go to big I think so if you'll help me
Frank asked me how already I mean they've
started opening the windows down the
Embarcadero. Getting Smart exchanges
clothes but he said we covered Oh I.
Sigh I was so rude a moment ago but
it's always discouraging to hear
a wife say that a husband loves
What do you write comic strips of
a more serious my life. But today I just.
Hope you find him as it doesn't think
NY is not going to make. One god that god.
Out of that I was walking out on the show
morning and make you want to belt from
the Oriental roof got out there. Listening
to one of the dancers from the show.
Maybe and Frank Sammy help
sometimes. I've found that I'm alone
after I just heard about it I'm sorry I
can't understand it expect says he was
happy we were doing great there was no
reason for it sometimes I don't know what
makes people tick even the ones closest to
him I just can't believe she killed well
maybe she did. Well it could
have been robbery she made
a surprise somebody in the
dressing room if you check
a step see if anything was missing
you know what do it now all.
We've been through almost all of these
places we still haven't gone to the don't
rank or are.
Good or are.
Or are.
Fine by look at the scope of the
man's quote mind if I look at it
a dollar. That's Frank's code where did
you get all your business but that's my
husband noticed by the game in your intro
to that coat with four dollars for
a duck macam when I open up this one way
to go out of line Oh I just sell stuff I
don't watch people at
the door as it was the.
Old or or.
You know and he is just
like nothing at home.
My. Heart and
a lot. I
never knew there were so many land going
sailors in the world all avoiding the
jackets seems facts.
Be. I might as well admit
I can't remember. That
much sun left find him and if you think
that he said his letter below with
fine. Danny maybe if I'm alone like
to give the house I got to go home anyway
and feed the dog been locked up all day.
Sure sure I could meet you later someplace
How about picking me up with one of my
government union streets when you're ready
not to try the way all right. To then
our. Looks like your shadow is
finally caught up with you.
I find. I beg your pardon there's no
need been to we might as well go to camp
Well come on at least we'll have.
At the time I think.
Hello Rembrandt's he was going
to than I was you again who
let you in landlord you mind you know they
just self home I love having cops move
in on the letter Don't pretend you don't
know what I'm talking about I mean the
letter your pal picked up
a heart went this morning I want to seize
all knows all except where Frank is with
the killer. And if you go back to jail
Rivers is leave me alone the merry go rounds
over this case is going cold on me and
you're the only live thing in it so from now
on I'm sticking with you that's just peachy
Oh I'm bushed you want to be covered
a lot of territory in
a day my men are foolish you should be
more considerate. You make anything out of
this letter pretty cryptic Not yet
but I'm working on it sounds like
a guy in love you think
the. Beyond me open
under the sun in the place like the one
where I've lost you. And I don't lay that
right in your lap it's not mean anything
to you I wish you did that you're not
bringing me my medicine Don't worry I'll
find it and I'll be right there with you
when you do where you go I will. Buy.
You insist upon going with me if I
will though I walk anyway there's
a man out front one and back and one on
the roof fine thing right here so I was
just waiting but it comes to you you can't
stand the strain any longer and go to.
Maybe you're right some think
you seem to have discovered
a lot of my friends I never knew before
in one day what you couldn't find out
before years I guess I was when. A lot
of it's my fault anyway. I hadn't
been much of a life. Mission from
you Mrs Johnson. You've got to get
a chance to be frank alone given and then
if you want to come in and I think it's
a pity but it's got to be his choice I want
to try and find someone the other what
I've read that is all right with me but
you've got to let me see him alone for I
haven't a bit and I'd
like to help you but I'm
a cop that Frank keeps on running
out of no witness to say nothing of
a job. Hungry
couldn't you
a thirty two couldn't figure out how to
work and are going to use your phone.
And I think I meant when he would go on
we've got results I think and one other.
But on.
The on. The air.
Or are. The
only thing I can think of.
I'm worried about Rembrandt was still
hungry and I will talk. Funny. Or or.
Was Made another to.
Like the what are you.
Your temperature is not thank you things
mean perfect you know I'm worried about Dr
he may be an angry perhaps
he should stay here for
a few days for observation magic in the
future exercise or Yes well the door across
. A DOT can talk.
The I wish you would look at him
a little I'm not there I'm your friend
myself I beg your pardon your wife enjoy it
leave without provocation is not my wife.
And I got you know the. President of
a check standing at the sink Why did Frank
and it's. One of the deceptive why not
me I'm
a chump I give it to anybody you bring it
to me why me but don't you mean you you
think there's
a reason something you missed something I
did. Drive right there just aren't once
OK.
Wery so.
Fresh. To Eleanor. Now I remember
one day on the beach to come out just
after we were married Frank made
a mermaid out of things it
was supposed to be me and
a big weight came up and washed it away and
well I've lost her and I think you will
never lose me Frank I won't let you that's
what he meant by letter it was the core
of seeing something for me you know where
he is I'll take you back there for us
once why. We're late.
I'm sorry to have to ask you to do this job
this man was found in the alley behind
a gentle on the Embarcadero
in Brooklyn. He was wearing
a trench coat he was wearing
a seaman Captain Jack. What I remember
I guess I could be him. I'm not sure.
That you make it about that case where.
You're.
Losing the war or.
That our law. Goes that
Raymond Case two witnesses.
To
a Ghost sent to. Hell
of anything that I could
say just the words.
That that was a prank. For
a quick moment I thought it was myself
inside that no I could see what was like
holding on. By Did my eyes I'm done. Why
don't we give freely of excellence.
If only I had another chance I
thought and I thought it was
a prank and I thank gosh relations in your
performance but it was an act I really
did think. Where is it at
then you'd like to think.
You were there when it happened
like that you talk. Johnson Dan's
a smart cookie. I want to watch you get
the idea past that step up there has
somebody at that time off sure
the guy she identified was
a second maid off the tank or just been
paid off somebody's role in Brazil why
wasn't I told the fingerprint report just.
To thank God I knucklehead get out of
that that is then check and
find out where they don't.
Imagine it was like that when
I went Yes I felt it was.
The right. With this one right away.
Oh you're from the Bay Area the on the
lookout for one yellow cab number three to
break the ice and some of the seven column
or nine seven six two that's all just as
awesome and six thirty pm EST.
Right down there beyond that railing and.
Then waiting for me or they think I
would remember I almost did I know.
A good doctor there is too many people read
in this guy's story Alex I know where I
can maybe went over.
The subject. Read another that you can
accept and only when they deny. All
knowledge of the article written. Like.
Yeah things begin to boil
when they write down
or go to the beach on my breath it's
like my eyes mist Garneau that smell.
The US.
I don't like the place. It's but.
It's coming out of the girl and I was
a kid more frightening than a
man. That's where love is when
a white does when they're
all at the bank will.
Surely want to start over again with you
as I'm sure I want to try and not sure
what he will suppose he doesn't want to and
I let him go you never know how I feel
about. It he thinks people
can turn back give it
a try. I know but. You're too cynical
chip that's too late now to change my
profession. To. Bring you know.
What's the matter with you don't you still
want to marry. Yes I got to have stood
by the way. You sent me but I want to see
Malone for just one of the money I talked
with Hello All right when you.
Get out there comes
a parasite they're making it down to fight
them already charred failing to have
this done in
a public bar I'm an Indian and. Oh
you know seventy seventy one. And I don't
want some Sunday Thank you take care of
things not to burn down and often years not
I've been doing all day riding back and
forth but haven't been there in Sausalito
on my own very little but I can't stick
around here in him I've got to.
Make up my head that it was.
Under US law. Is the key to my car
the thing is funded over the Partly.
By Sam I get about it better.
They finally played. Frank Johnson.
For are.
Sorry Mr Johnson but I had to be careful
Frank window names I couldn't when Milan
are going on to my car but by men who want
to go over the pike not in their limited
way thank you.
I lost the bet with. What it.
Has already delivered
later changed. The lives.
It's going to look like.
And I'd likely get.
To tell me about tried. To talk as
I make a big deal of it. It was
a silly thing to do writing that morning
no sounded like it had it that literally.
By the time I finished the drinks on the
letter I said Gary. Can hide out here
for which you want to. Get a
job in another town rebel and
a time to get artist. We've
got to pull out. We.
Describe as cool juncture I can
get an account. Very far of it
seven dollars seventy one cents or
that nigga is a felon and I get
a record ready to help him find his promise
to give you the next it's money little
I can well it's a promise if
it's worth it so I love give to
a risen over the road to come on Actually
you turn around you know an artist named
Frank Johnson Oh thank God.
Life didn't get you I thought
it could be but I don't remember
Well Jan you were. Able to get no.
The over there of the really close to go
all the way then the walking dead in on
that OK getting
a. Card or going to bed and it was all let
me just know I've never been with you
you can you know why I
can't let in to know.
What I think and now
whenever that man shouted.
You know that when. There is.
Nobody else knows. The fine.
Thanks America.
My problem rather than just just working
to call it chance has passed me.
All I haven't done time to talk to him now
that's McDonald and Murray but he said
there are some information you want to
hold on hello inspector remember you asked
me to check all of Suzy's things to see if
anything was missing I mean I'm busy of
causing him I just wanted to tell you that
nothing was missing except that sketch
of Frank you on the back of
a man you get I don't know but Sue said it
looked like that newspaper man that was
in the club this afternoon
with Mrs Johnson. Comics. Now.
I mean. I have always frank he's
on his way to me too there is
a deal with the drug. But that's the
thing I'm more with a plan it's
a pretty sharp fall of. Zero for men with.
Men and women running.
Around
a little of course but the
things I think. I am trying.
Thing again are not really.
Anything in
a way. You. Really. Write
it only takes a couple of minutes
sighs really get to the top we see
a prankster so we might see that by now.
Believe. Me it.
Was Really.
Anybody would eventually.
Eat.
Right and the only. Way
to stand for another
radical she would have
a friend in Little League with their
side together would be too conspicuous
a terrorist base you hear the sound
to some of its value to. Radio or
get all get it right you know I.
Get that unless we try to kill it.
The only. Way that any.
Meaning. We.
Need.
We. Bring. Right judge.
You Mr Leggett. Let loose Michael. I know.
You want to get.
Left. You get
a better. Chance than to.
Win
a case of. The
same.
Like the right of the the fact the only.
The
clothes the old
old. Old.
The the. Old old.
The it were.
Older or. You
going to do
a good job. Like it down there I've been
faced with this rank up there on the
midwife. The door. And
the
real. World.
The and. The the
the the the
at the or the or
OR. The.